<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MEDVISOR</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">This Privacy Policy describes how [Your Company Name] ("we," "our," or "us") collects, uses, and shares information when you use our website or services. By using our website or services, you consent to the data practices described in this policy.\n\nInformation We Collect:\n\nPersonal Information: We may collect personal information such as your name, email address, and phone number when you voluntarily provide it to us.\nUsage Data: We automatically collect information about your device and how you interact with our website or services, such as your IP address, browser type, and pages visited.\nCookies: We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to improve your experience on our website and to analyze usage patterns.\n\nHow We Use Your Information:\n\nWe may use the information we collect for various purposes, including to provide and improve our services, communicate with you, personalize your experience, and comply with legal obligations.\n\nSharing of Information:\n\nWe may share your information with third-party service providers who help us operate our website or provide services to you. We may also share information as required by law or to protect our rights or the rights of others.\n\nYour Choices:\n\nYou can choose not to provide certain information or opt out of certain data collection practices. However, this may limit your ability to use certain features of our website or services.\n\nSecurity:\n\nWe take reasonable measures to protect the information we collect from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.\n\nChanges to this Policy:\n\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this page, and we encourage you to review this Policy periodically.</string>

    <string name="terms_of_service_text">These Terms of Service ("Terms") govern your use of [Your Company Name]\'s website and services. By accessing or using our website or services, you agree to be bound by these Terms.\n\nUse of Services:\n\nYou may use our website and services for lawful purposes only. You agree not to use our website or services in any way that violates any applicable laws or regulations.\n\nIntellectual Property:\n\nAll content on our website, including text, graphics, logos, and images, is the property of [Your Company Name] or its licensors and is protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws. You may not use, reproduce, or distribute any content from our website without our prior written consent.\n\nDisclaimer of Warranties:\n\nOur website and services are provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis, without any warranties of any kind, either express or implied. We do not guarantee that our website or services will be uninterrupted or error-free.\n\nLimitation of Liability:\n\nIn no event shall [Your Company Name] be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, arising out of or in connection with your use of our website or services.\n\nGoverning Law:\n\nThese Terms shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of [Your Jurisdiction], without regard to its conflict of law principles.\n\nChanges to Terms:\n\nWe reserve the right to update or modify these Terms at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on our website. Your continued use of our website or services after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms.</string>
</resources>
